(Sheldon:)Thank my friend, Wil Wheaton.
(Sheldon:)For your information,
I have nine friends.
(Sheldon:)Ten if we include you.
(Sheldon:)Nine it is.
Eh, it's ten.
I'll count Wolowitz.
(Sheldon:)-Hello, friend Leonard.
-Hoy, you're in a good mood.
(Sheldon:)I'm in a great mood.
(Leonard:)Well, you're about to be
in an even better one.
(Leonard:)I didn't want to say anything
until I knew for sure, but...
(Leonard:)I've been re-running the tests
on your element in my lab
(Leonard:)and I disproved it.
Your element does not exist!
(Sheldon:)Yeah, but what about
the Chinese research team?
(Sheldon:)They found it.
(Leonard:)Yeah, it turns out someone added
simulated signals to the data files.
(Leonard:)They faked the results.
(Sheldon:)Really?
Yes!
Do you know what that means?
It means that all of this
attention that you hate goes away.
(Sheldon:)-So no more interviews?
-No, it's all over.
(Sheldon:)-I can't believe it.
-Well, you're welcome.
(Sheldon:)You robbed me
of my greatest achievement!